Chapter 3: Platform 9 3/4

Harry's parents had made him go to Platform 9 and ¾ this year, over his protests. Apparently he needed to "socialize with the other children". Instead of driving all the way to London, he had just taken the Floo. Stepping out of the fireplace, he looked around the platform. There was already a small horde of children and parents, and there was still two hours until the train left. He looked around to see if any non-NPCs were here yet. Well, Draco was sitting at a table on the other side of the platform.

"Hello Draco."

"Potter." Malfoy snarled.

"Are you no longer my friend?"

Draco replied "Generally, killing someone's father means that."

"I've already told you why I killed him. He was a Death-Eater who was trying to kill me. What would you have me do? Die?"

"Yes. You killed my father, you are no longer my friend."

"You hit me with a torture curse, and I was still your friend."

"Right, because mildly hurting someone is the same as killing their father."

"Again, it was self defense. So you're not going to be my friend."

"Again, No."

"Very well."

"Hello Harry."

"Hey Hermione. What did you do this summer?"

"I studied for the O. with you. You should know that."

"Hey, what classes are you taking?"

"Fourth Year Defense and Herbology, Third Year Runes, Divination, Care of Magical Creatures, and History of Magic, Fifth Year Charms, Transfiguration, Potions, and Astronomy and Sixth Year Arithmancy . And you?

"Third Year Herbology and Care of Magical Creatures, Fourth Year Defense and Potions, Fifth Year Charms and Transfiguration, and Seventh Year Astronomy and Arithmancy."

"Do you know if Neville is here?"

"I don't see him, do you?"

"No. Hey, there's that girl from the Quibbler."

"Wait. Luna Lovegood?"

"Yeah."

"I need to talk to her."

"Why?"

"Well, she published an article where she claimed Sirius Black and Peter Pettigrew are secretly the same person, and that I was 65 years old."

"So? Why would-Oh. How did she know that?"

"I think she's a seer, and given that I am trying to take over the world, having her on my side would be very helpful."

"Well then go over and talk to her."

Luna was certainly the most oddly dressed person in the entire, purely by default. She was wearing a helmet at least three sizes too large, that was painted a shade of neon orange. Her shirt was lime green, and seemed to be made of basilisk skin. She also appeared to be on stilts. Finally, the magazine she was reading was turn sideways, and was written in hieroglyphics. There were also no other children within 20 feet of her.

"Hello Luna. I'm Harry Potter."

"Good morning Tom."

"How do you know that?"

"It isn't wise to tell everyone your secrets."

"Fine. Muffliato. Now can you tell me how you know?"

"Well, since Avada Kedavra doesn't blow up houses, and always works, it is clear that the Dark Lord didn't try to Avada Kedavra. Given that rituals, if gone wrong can cause explosions, it is obvious that it was a ritual. Combine that with the unusual way you acted at Diagon Alley-".

Harry made a faint sputtering noise.

"-and my prior knowledge of mind replacement rituals, it is obvious that Voldemort replaced your mind with his own."

"What."

"It is obvious that Voldemort replaced your mind with his own. You do know that right?"

"Yeah, but, well there's no way you know that." Harry replied.

"What do you mean? I just told you I know?"

"I mean, it only makes sense in hindsight. Even with what you knew, you had to be guessing. Plus, I looked at the predictions in the Quibbler, and less than half of them are true."

"As far as you know."

"Also, how did you know that Voldemort and Tom Riddle were the same person. He didn't tell anyone that."

"Tom Riddle was a prominent and gifted who was the same age as Voldemort. That's obvious."

"Okay. How are you this smart, and are you trying to take over the world?

"My parents conducted rituals to boost my intelligence and intuition, and not yet, and probably never."

"Wait, you can do that?"

"Yes, but it's extremely dangerous, and only works before the age of 7."

"Would you be willing to help someone take over the world?"

"It depends on why they are trying."

"To stop people from dying."

"Sure, where do you plan to start?"

"I didn't tell you I was trying to take over the world."

"I didn't ask."

Chapter 6: Backdoor Deals

Backdoor Deals

After talking to the members of the Wizengamot, Harry had learnt that there were only three he needed to convince on his side. With Amelia Bones breaking ties, he only needed two, and fewer still if he could get someone from Greengrass's faction on his side.

Michael Oliver was the Lord of the Noble House of Oliver. He was 82 years old, and had three children and seven grandchildren. He was also a pureblood, a Slytherin, and adamantly opposed to elective seats.

"Hello Lord Oliver. I wanted to you about the elective seats. Why are you opposed to it?"

"Young man, I'm all for letting the people have a voice, but they have that in the Minister. Letting the rabble rule this distinguished body would ruin it. "

"Lord Oliver, the people of Britain are quite capable of making decisions on their own. The Minister has no real power, and you know that. Letting the people have actual influence is reasonable.

"I'm fine with the people having influence, young man. You plan to have thirty seats ran by the people though. That is far too much influence. You'd let the rabble have enough to stop anything they didn't like. We cannot be Aceh."

"How is letting 90% of the people have a third of the power giving them too much?"

"I will not let the mob control this body. I would be amenable to your suggestion if there were fewer seats."

"So if there were twenty seats you would vote for it."

"Yes."

"Very well."

"So, Harry, will Lord Oliver vote with us?" Amelia Bones asked.

"Only if we reduce it to twenty seats. What about Lord Nelson and Lady Raines." Harry replied.

"Lord Nelson will, Lady Raines will not. I believe we have 42 votes. Are you willing to reduce it to 20 seats?"

"Maybe. I'm going to see if Lady and Lord Greengrass will vote with us."

"Good."

"Hello Lord and Lady Greengrass. I trust you are well."

"Yes. Mr. Potter. What do you want to talk with us about?" The Lord Greengrass answered.

"Will you support the adding to thirty elected seats to the Wizengamot?"

"Possibly. Why would we?" asked the Lady Greengrass.

"Times are changing. My side currently has three quarters of the Wizengamot, and after this passes I will have yet more. You vote with me in this, and you take a important place in the new order. If you don't, I can still pass this, and there are ways to take the Most Anciente title from a house."

"Very well." The Lord Greengrass replied. "We will side with you on this. If you give us ten thousand Galleons."

"Done."

"What? You're willing to pay that much?"

"Yeah. I can write a contract if you want, or just give you the money out of my vault ."

"Very well. We'll vote with you." The Lady Greengrass said.

"Now that we have filled the vacant seats, we will now turn to our last order of business for today. Lord Potter has another proposal."

"As many know, I propose that we add another twenty seats to this distinguisged body. They will be filled by dividing Britain into twenty areas of equal population, and then holding elections for each area."

"An interesting proposal, Lord Potter. Does anyone have any questions, or shall we call this to a vote? Very well, let us vote."

There were a number of wands lit, but Harry could not count quite how many.

"Forty one, forty two, forty three, forty four, forty five. I belive that the vote is 45-11. The motion passes. The Ministry shall be authorized to create the new districts."

From one side of the room there were cheers, and from the other screams of outrage. An old man in gray robes leapt up, and screamed "You will ruin the Wizengamot with mudbloods and blood traitors."

"Silence." Amelia Bones yelled. "The motion has passed, and we will not kill each other over it. In accordance with the last decision of the eighty-eighth Wizengamot, let us adjourn."

Chapter 7: Hogwarts Pt 2

Hogwarts Part 2

The next day Harry had to get up early to go to his classes. He had 8 of his 9 classes today, everything but Astronomy, and Care of Magical Creatures started at 8:30 on the far end of the school. He had had to practically inhale his breakfast, and then run over to the class.

Near the outskirts of the Forest, there were a group of third year Gryffindor's and Hufflepuffs milling around, and a grizzled old man missing a leg whom Harry assumed was Professor Kettleburn.

"Ah, our other Second Year. You're very nearly late." The Professor growled.

"I'm sorry Professor." Harry replied. Harry walked over to where Hermione was standing. "I think I need to something about Luna."

"Why? She agreed to join you on your plan."

"Yes, but she's also intelligent, dangerous, and possibly insane. I think I should try to get her to swear an unbreakable vow."

"How would you get the magic to do that?"

"There were a lot of prisoners in Azkaban."

"Why do you need to get her to swear a vow? You didn't try to get me to swear one."

"Yes, but that was because Voldemort trusted you. You wouldn't destroy the world, and getting you to swear a Vow would impair your advice. Luna could try something, and end up destroying the world, especially if I teach her about Science."

"I guess that's a good idea. Any ideas on where to take over first?"

"I really don't think we should be talking about this in public."

"No one is listening." Hermione replied.

"I don't want to take the chance."

"Muffliato. Now, do you have any ideas?"

"I'm thinking Austria first."

"Austria? Why? They're a French ally, and we need France."

"For one, Emperor Francis is rather unpopular, so the people there would probably support us. Francis has close ties to the German leadership, so they'd probably try to place him back up on his throne. That'd scare the French enough that they'd probably help us depose of the German Emperor, especially since the Chambre d'assistants Estimés doesn't like Francis very much. Then Spain would probably join with us. We'd have a huge power bloc."

" Huh. If that works, you'd be the most powerful player in Europe. It sounds pretty risky though." Hermione replied.

"Even if worst comes to worst, we can always beat the French too."

"Don't get overconfident."

"Ah, everyone is here. Please come over here to see our first creature, the Niffler." Professor Kettleburn called.

Potions, Arithmancy, Herbology, and History had been normal enough, though many of the students had been surprised at the "little kid" in their classes. At 2:45, Harry arrived in the defense classroom, still half-asleep from the History of Magic. There were a number of 4th year Slytherins and Hufflepuffs sitting in the seats, and a vaguely lupine man wearing patchy clothes standng in the center of the room. Harry sat next to Hermione, who had come from Potions. A few minutes later, Remus Lupin stood up.

"My predecessor, David Monroe, was respected by all of you. I'm sorry to say that he also gave you dangerously wrong information. David Monroe gave you a long lecture, where he taught you that one killing curse will kill anything. This is dangerously wrong. None of you can cast the killing curse. It requires an amount of magic that none of you yet have. It also requires you to hate whoever you are casting it at, to want them to die. If a dragon, or a troll, or a basilisk attacks, you may not be able to cast the killing curse. The Killing Curse is a tool. It is a useful tool, but it is also difficult to cast and thoroughly illegal. There is a reason why Aurors in battle do not simply cast the Killing Curse. Last year, two of the students in this classroom faced a troll. If they had simply followed Monroe's advice, they both would have died. Instead, Mr. Potter came up with an ingenious method to kill the troll. That is what combat is about. Combat is not taking one spell, and then saying it is the answer to every problem."

Most students in the room looked shocked. Harry got up and applauded.

"Now, I will be continuing David Monroe's practice of battles and armies. I will however, be making a few changes to the rules. Actual battles are fought over objectives, not just two armies dumped into the woods and forced to fight. Actual people have motivations of their own. The first battle will be in three weeks, on September 24th. Generals will be picked by their armies, not vice versa. Now, let's review the Stunning Spell.

Chapter 9: PMC

The next weekend, Harry began the Vienna operation.

His plan was to hire a private mercenary, and use them to overthrown Emperor Francis of the Austrian Empire. He was first going to meet with Ironlance, a mercenary company of 50 soldiers, most of whom were from the Brazilian Empire. He was meeting with the head of the company Pedro Goulart, after being transfigured to look like an adult.

"Hello, Mr. Duke. What do you wish to hire my company for?" Major Goulart asked.

"I would like to hire Ironlance to attack the Austrian Emperor's palace, and overthrow their government. I also wish to hire you as security for a few months after we overthrow Francis." Harry responded.

"That will be difficult. Francis has an army, you know." Goulart replied

"I'm willing to pay war rates."

"Why do you want to overthrow Francis?" Goulart questioned.

"He's an unjust ruler, and he oppresses his people." Harry replied.

Goulart smiled. Clearly Mr. Duke was just another idealistic fool. He'd be able to make quite a bit of money from him, and Francis wasn't that dangerous.

"Very well. My price is a million Galleons."

"A million Galleons. You could buy a country with that much money." Harry replied. It was a ridiculous price, of course. He also had unlimited money, so it was no matter.

"Isn't that what you're doing?"

"Okay. I'll get Urk to write up a contract. "

Goulart started in surprise. Just how much money did Mr. Duke have?

"Okay. When do you plan for us to start?"

"On the 4th of this month."

Chapter 10: Vienna, Pt 1

On the Fourth of October, Mr. Duke gave a speech to prepare the troops.

"Everyone, we will be deposing Emperor Francis today. We'll begin by taking a Portkey I have managed to acquire to the Magical Disrict of Vienna. Then we will stun everyone we see, proceed to the Throne Room, and kill the Emperor. After we have secured the Government building, I'll come to the Palace, and I'll begin to set up a new government. You will provide security during this. Does everyone get that?"

The assembled soldiers nodded.

"Then proceed to the Portkey outside."

Gottfried Essen was bored. Guard duty in the Palace was monotonous, but it was good pay. It was three in the morning, and he was close to nodding off. He should probably get a potion. Well, at least he didn't have to guard the Emperor. Francis was not a nice man. He thought he heard a banging noise outside.

Suddenly, dozens of Brazilian soldiers burst through the door.

Eleutrio Goeuvia yelled out "Drop your wands and surrender."

Gottfried heard the man next to him scream an expletive. There was a clatter of wands on the floor. The Brazilians began stunning his fellow soldiers. This was not what he had signed up for. He dropped his wand and yelled "I surrender." A Brazilian cast a stunner his way, and that was the last Gottfried Essen remembered of the first battle of Vienna.

Emperor Francis thought he heard a faint noise outside. He wondered what was happening. As he was getting up, groaning all the way, he saw a flash of light from under his door. The door burst open, and a dozen swarthy men, who seemed to be Brazilian, burst in. "What is this?" Francis called. "Goodbye Francis. Reducto." One of the men replied. And so, Emperor Francis, ruler of the Austrian Empire since 1945, died.

Harry stepped onto the soil of his first conquest. Some of the Austrians had tried to counterattack, but most had surrendered after Francis's death and the capture of most of government. All told, only 2 members of the Ironlance had died, and 6 were badly injured. The rest were rich. And Harry, well Harry begun the first step on the path to world conquest. Now for Germany.

Chapter 11: Vienna, Pt 2

Vienna, Part 2

By Saturday, a new provisional government had been set up. A few of Harry's associates and members of the British government had taken roles in the new Vienna. Mr. Duke had been able to go back to school, after a brief "sickness". Harry had called a meeting of those in the know.

In the depths of Merlin Hospital, Harry asked "What do you think our plan for after the German War should be?"

Moody replied "Son, you don't even know that the Germans will go to war yet. Don't make plans for victory before you've even started the game."

Harry responded "They will."

Mad-Eye sighed. "You don't know that. Yes, you were successful in Vienna, but you easily could have failed. You don't know everything."

Harry replied "True, but the Germans have to attack us. And besides, I have a plan."

"Son, you're treating this like one of your games. It isn't. If you lose in one of those, nothing happens. If you lose in this, you, and all of us, die. Let the actual professionals handle the war."

Harry answered "I am a professional. I won in Vienna, and I'm the leader of this."

Mad-Eye growled "You're twelve. At some point, your overconfidence is going to cause you to get us all killed. Let me handle the war."

Harry replied "No."

Mad-Eye growled "Then I'm leaving."

One's of the Emperor aides called out "The Intelligence Minister is here, sir."

Karl Hollweg, the Intelligence Minister of the German Empire, was a short and squat man, who appeared to be in his late nineties.

Emperor Frederich asked "What news do you have for you have for me today?"

"Well", Minister Hollweg responded "we now have definitive evidence that the British were behind the Vienna coup. "

"Ah. What is it?"

"The force that attacked Vienna and deposed your uncle was Ironlance, a private mercenary company composed of mostly Brazilians. They were hired by a "Mr. Duke", who is the fictional identity of one of the members of the new british government. Incidentally, we have found out how much "Mr. Duke" paid Ironlance.

"How much?" the Emperor questioned.

"A million Galleons." Karl responded with a smug smile.

"A million? How?"

"I'm not sure, Sir, but I think it has to do with the unlimited budget the British seem to have gotten recently." Inwardly, he smirked.

"Ah. Well, we'll raise this at the next meeting of the International Confederation of Wizards." The Emperor replied.

"I don't think the Brits will cede this."

"Of course not. But we will have a Casus Belli, and then we will go to war with them." The Emperor said smugly, acting like it was his idea.

"Ah. You plan to attack London?"

"Yes, and Hogwarts, and their new hospital. We shall seize all of Britain."

"Ah. That sounds like an excellent plan. In other news…..

That night, in the streets of Berlin, Karl Hollweg walked. After a few minutes, he ducked in an alleyway. "He" removed a charm around himself. A young looking blond woman walked out, with a smirk. All was going to plan.

Chapter 12: The ICW

The next week, both Harry and the German Emperor went to the meeting of the International Confederation of Wizards.

The Sabase Praacheen Hol towered over everything around. Nearly a hundred meters tall, it loomed vast over the great city around it. The shining jewel of India was unspeakably ancient. None had yet tried to use Muggle methods to date it, but what methods they had used had revealed a date that was simply unimaginable. The Sabase Praacheen Hol was over 4 million years old. Given that most wizards had believed that the world was ten thousand years old, this had come as quite a shock. It seemed to be a relic from the times of Atlantis. The walls were made of a glowing white material, which nothing of this day was even able to so much as scratch. It was one of the greatest artifacts of the days when gods yet walked the Earth, when Oinos Bhrghos destroyed countries with a word.

What was inside was far less impressive. There was row after row of seats, fit to hold the hundred and more magical nations that deigned to send representatives to the International Confederation of Wizards. There were also smaller conference rooms, for the numerous subcommittees. Inside the room for the subcommittee, there was indecipherable writing carved into the walls in some long forgotten language. As near as Harry could tell, it read Fch chmhchdch obrchn Latnts. Across the room, Harry saw the Emperor Frederich, and a middle-aged man who seemed to be his aide.

A few minutes later, the chair, an old seeming woman in a headscarf, probably from the Ottomans, said, "I see everyone is here this week. Are there any issues anyone wants to raise?"

The Emperor Frederich jumped up, and shouted, "Yes. Britain has launched an illegal coup against Austria, and they must be reprimanded."

Cagri Sadik responded "Ah. How does the representative of the British Empire respond?"

Harry said, "Let me do this." To Amelia Bones. He got up. "This charge is of course, ridiculous." There were mutters of surprise. "The deposing of Emperor Francis was not an act of the British government. The organization that killed that senile old tyrant merely asked for our help. And Frederich's concern for Emperor Francis is not born out of any high-minded altruism. Rather, it is because the death of his uncle, and the replacement of him with a regime that will actually listen to the people, means that Frederich will lose some of his ill-gotten and illegal influence in Germany. Any German invasion of Austria would be a sign of German revanchism."

The Emperor indignantly replied "Are we no longer safe in our beds from Britain? Francis was the legitimate ruler of Austria, and murdering him is an act of war. I demand all British forces leave Austria, or we will declare war."

"And if we were to leave, who would succeed to the Austrian throne? Oh, right, you. This is not some high-minded altruism; this is a simple desire to expand his throne. I call on all of you to stop this German expansionism in its tracks."

"You dare defy me, you impudent boy?" Frederich screamed, practically apoplectic.

"Yes. I will not stand idly by while the Germans again take nations, and try to found a European Empire. I do not wish to fight another great war, but I will if I must."

"Then you will have your war, and I will defeat you."

"No." The French representative called.

"What?"

"You heard me. You will not conquer Britain, and we will fight you to prevent you. You lost the first Great War, do you really wish to fight another?"

"This is not another Great War. I will fight to stop this boy from killing us in our beds."

"It is a great war. You are threating to invade countries to expand your throne. If you defeat Britain, where will you turn next? France? Spain? Poland? The Italian States?"

"Nowhere. I fight only Britain. I promise that."

"Grindlewald promised the same after Poland fifty years ago. And there were those in my country who were foolish enough to believe him. I was not. I will not be foolish enough to believe you."

"You will do this?"

"I told you." Harry called with a smirk.

"You." The Emperor screamed. "I will kill you foolish boy." Emperor Frederich stormed out.

Cagri Sadik tried to restore order, but that was a fool's errand. As Harry left the room, there were only two people with a smile on their face.